dvdvideosoft.com 2012-12-22

# DVDVideoSoft.com: Download free DVD, iPod, YouTube video converter and editor software and freeware

Since your privacy is important to us, DVDVideoSoft Ltd has created this privacy statement in order to let you know our firm commitment to your privacy.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for DVDVideoSoft Ltd websites http://dvdvideosoft.com/

## Information collection

Our programs do not collect any kind of personal information.

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information") or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you buy Rocket Subscription for our software, or you want to provide us with your personal data, to give us the opportunity to get in touch with you.

When you enter a contest or other promotional event, we may ask for information such as your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

When you buy Rocket Subscription, we may ask you for information such as your name, e-mail address, shipping address, and serial number.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and your time spent at our sites, and to gather broad demographic information. This allows us to see which parts of our sites users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means, for instance, that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will remain anonymous. We do not use this information for any other purposes.

When a user submits personal information, it is kept on a private server not accessible from the Internet. This limits the possibility of any malicious use of your information.

## Use of personal information

DVDVideoSoft Ltd may share non-personal, summary information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties. However, for partners or third parties under contract with DVDVideoSoft Ltd, any individual customer information provided may be used solely to perform or complete a necessary transaction or function related to the customer's purchase. These transactions or functions shall be in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement.

DVDVideoSoft Ltd will not share any individual customer information outside of the contracted partners and third parties mentioned above, without first receiving the individual's prior written approval. In short, DVDVideoSoft Ltd does not sell users' personal information to lists. In some cases, DVDVideoSoft Ltd may use a visitor's personal information to understand overall patterns for site usage, to contact the user for clarification on inaccurate information, or to follow up on a customer service issue. Personal information may include name, address, telephone number, etc. 

DVDVideoSoft Ltd may send the user information or updates about special offers, programs, new products and/or services via e-mail. The user are able to unsubscribe from the mailing list any time after receiving the first information message.

## Links to other sites

This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that DVDVideoSoft Ltd is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web Sites as well as any information they might collect, even though our name or logo may appear on those sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the Privacy Statements of each and every Web site that you visit, as the privacy policy of those sites may differ from ours. Our Privacy Statement applies solely to http://dvdvideosoft.com.

## Use of "cookies"

During your visit to our website, so-called "cookies" are saved to your computer. These "cookies" register information about the navigation of your computer on our website (loaded pages, date, time of day and length of visit etc.) which we can access during your next visit in order to adapt the website to your personal requirements and optimize loading times. We also use this information to enter your data into enquiry forms and suchlike so that you do not need to fill them in yourself again and again.

We never store passwords or similarly sensitive data in cookies. The use of cookies is common and advantageous. Cookies are used on most larger websites. By indicating how and when visitors use a website, cookies aid us in finding out which areas are popular and which areas are not. Many improvements and updates are based on information supplied by cookies. Cookies can also help us to personalize web content and meet the desires of our visitors.

Our websites do not use cookies to collect personal information from your computer that was not initially sent as a cookie.

You have the option to control the acceptance of cookies yourself and, if you wish, to block them entirely by configuring your browser as follows:

If you use the Internet Explorer to surf the net: In the "Tools" menu, click "Internet Options", select the "Privacy" tab and click "Advanced". Here, you can "Block" cookies or set up a "Prompt". The latter setting allows you to decide from occasion to occasion whether you would like to accept a cookie or not.
